Maremont, Mark collection on the 1996 Teamsters election controversy 6348
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Mark Maremont collection on the 1996 Teamsters election controversy
1995- 1997
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Maremont, Mark
International Brotherhood of Teamsters
6348
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records.
7954191
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives 227 Ives Hall Tower Road Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheelref@cornell.edu https://catherwood.library.cornell.edu/kheel/
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, March 07, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 07, 2016
Labor unions -- Elections; Maremont, Mark; International Brotherhood of Teamsters
7954191
- Mike Royko (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Mike Royko (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Organized Crime and Labor-Movement; Racketeering in the United States, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Independent Review Board Report of Investigation of General President Ronald Carey, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Michigan State Membership Rosters and Distributions Severance and Retirement Fund, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Roach. Christopher, 1994-1997 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- IBT Local 710 Pension Fund Annual Report, 1994-1997 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Richard Leebove and George Geller, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- General Conference Vs. IBT. Testimony of George Geller (Box 1, Folder 8)
- General Conference Vs. IBT. Testimony of George Geller, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Central Conference Vs. IBT: Testimony of Richard Leebove, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Report of Ron Carey's Corruption and Failure, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Hoffa '96 Restore Teamster Power, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Office of the Election Officer; Pre Election Protests, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Reform, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Brothers in the Hood: Tales From the Teamsters 25th Convention, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Chris Bohner. Jimmy Hoffa Junior, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Michael Belzer/ NYSSILR. Election Office Case P-880-IBT-MGN, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Teamsters Office of the Election Officer, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Campaign Contributions, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Teamsters Local 337: Labor Organization Annual Report Form LM-2, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Election Officer Case Post-39, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- A Referendum on Union Democracy, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- November Fraud Conspiracy, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Robert Wages Affidavit, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Lyndon LaRouche, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Cash and Carey. Corruption Surrounding Former President Ron Carey, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Election Officer's Application for Approval Proposed Rerun election Plan, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Election Officer's Decisions, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Office of the Election Officer Case PR-027, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Carey Slate. Decision of the Election Appeals Master, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Election Officer's Decisions, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Independent Review Board Proposed Changes Against Ronald Carey, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- The Ron Carey Campaign Investigation, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Carey Slate. Election Office Case PR-035-EOH(Post-47-EOH) (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Jackie Presser Testimony to PCOC, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Clippings File (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Miscellaneous Page (Box 1, Folder 36)